"My name is Howard.
I can make your hair into diamonds.
(Raj:)My mom is morbidly obese.
Everybody love me."
(Howard:)Whoa, where is that coming from?
(Raj:)I'll tell you where it's coming from.
(Raj:)All you do is make fun of me
for coming to girls' night,
(Raj:)and now you're here ruining it
for everyone.
(Penny:)Raj, cool it.
He's gonna make us hair diamonds.
(Howard:)How am I ruining anything?
(Howard:)I'm just trying to help you
make better jewelry.
But this isn't about the jewelry.
(Raj:)This is about me having a place where
I can open up about my feelings.
(Howard:)Since when can't you open up
with me?
(Raj:)There are just some things
(Raj:)that I feel more comfortable
sharing with the girls,
(Raj:)because they won't make fun of me
(Raj:)or and call me names, or ask me if my
"Koothrapanties are in a bunch."
(Howard:)Buddy, I was just joking around.
(Raj:)Yeah, well,
sometimes your jokes hurt.
(Howard:)You're right.
(Howard:)I didn't realize
I was making you feel that way.
(Howard:)It was very brave of you to tell me.
(Raj:)Thank you.